Hi, I'm Jennifer Cail.
Before we start cleaning let's go over our supplies and detail.
First we're going to have a pair of gloves.
This will help protect your hands and also allow you to use a hotter temperature of water then otherwise, you would be able to with bare hands.
You also need a sponge.
You need a nice soft sponge you don't want anything that is too abrasive.
Otherwise it could scratch the cooking surface or different parts of your stove.
We're going to use a nice all purpose cleaner.
This would be useful when getting out any greasy spots on your stove.
I'm just using a generic environmentally friendly one.
You can use pretty much any type that you want as long as it's nice, gentle and it doesn't have any harsh chemicals which it could edge the stove top if you have ceramic or glass.
I'm going to have some baking soda.
This will help as a mild scrubbing agent in case you have any stubborn cooked on stains that you want to get rid of.
Then last but not least I'm going to have some hot water.
The nice hot water will help dissolve some of the more stubborn cooked on spots on our stove top.
It's all environmentally friendly so let's get started.